Guide to the Stanford in Germany Reunion Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford in Germany reunion collection
1958-2001
SC0941
Stanford University. Overseas Study Program.
0.25 Linear feet
This collection includes materials from several classes of students who participated in Stanford's overseas program in Beutelsbach, Germany; they were identified as Group I, II, etc. Materials from Group I (1958 program) consist of two CDs of audio recordings (The Boerner Tapes) from 4 events celebrating the end of the first program, which include student remarks and interviews, songs and skits, and a farewell talk by Dr. Peter Boerner; and memorabilia from their 2008 reunion in Germany. Materials from Group II (1959) consist of a CD of scanned images from 1959 and their 2008 reunion; and reminiscences printed from their website, 2008. Materials from Group XVIII (1967) consist of their 40th Anniversary Memory Book, pdf of the book on disc, and 2 clippings from German newspapers about their reunion in Germany, 2007.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
This collection includes materials from several classes of students who participated in Stanford's overseas program in Beutelsbach, Germany; they were identified as Group I, II, etc. Materials from Group I (1958 program) consist of two CDs of audio recordings (The Boerner Tapes) from 4 events celebrating the end of the first program, which include student remarks and interviews, songs and skits, and a farewell talk by Dr. Peter Boerner; and memorabilia from their 2008 reunion in Germany. Materials from Group II (1959) consist of a CD of scanned images from 1959 and their 2008 reunion; and reminiscences printed from their website, 2008. Materials from Group XVIII (1967) consist of their 40th Anniversary Memory Book, pdf of the book on disc, and 2 clippings from German newspapers about their reunion in Germany, 2007.
Access Terms
Boerner, Peter.
Collection Contents
- Records (Box 1)
  - Group I: The Boerner Tapes, 1958-2008; 2 optical disc(s) (CD) (Box 1.1U)
  - Group I: Reunion, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Group II: Memoirs, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Group II: Scanned Photos, 1959, 2008; 180 computer file(s)
  - Group XVIII 40th Anniversary memory book, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2012-021
  - Beutelsbacher Heimatbuch (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reunion photograph, 2011 Sep 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alumni biographies (Box 1, Folder 3)